Bhavnesh Arora Full Stack Web Developer



3 7206926954

Palwal,Haryana

in bhavnesh-arora

bhavnesh1811

Portfolio

Professional Summary

Passionate full stack web developer with a zest for solving complex problems using a wide range of front-end and back-end skills like HTML,CSS, JavaScript etc. A very enthusiastic and pro-active person for learning new things.1000+ hours of experience of coding and good in building projects with teams as well.

Education

Full Stack Web Development(Full Time)

Masai School

05/2022 - Present

B.Tech (Civil Engineering)

Satya College of Engg. & Technology 05/2011 - 05/2015

Soft Skills

Teamwork | Problem Solving | Adaptable

Technical Skills

React | Chakra UI | JavaScript | HTML CSS | GitHub | DSA

Projects

Apple TV+ Clone (StreamSpot) GitHub

- StreamSpot is an online video streaming website which allows users to stream movie trailers
- This is an individual project completed in 5 days.

Features:- Login, Responsive Homepage, Single Movie Page, Search Movie, Watch Trailer after Login

Techstack:- React, Chakra UI, React Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Render Server

Nykaa Clone GitHub

- Nykaa Clone is an ecommerce website inspired from original Nykaa fashion, beauty and wellness product website.
- It is a collaborative project of five members which is completed in 5 days.

Areas of Resposibility:-

Created men's and facewash Page.
 Developed sorting functionality on facewash page

Techstack:- HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Professional Experience

Supervisor

VN Engineering Company 07/2020-05/2022

Site Engineer

Alaska Infratech Private Limited 02/2018-01/2020

Civil Engineer

Samanvya Infrastructure Private Limited 05/2016-07/2017